<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<!--
    Storyline: Hidden Threat
	Version:   1.0
    Autor:     Longreed
	Last Edit: 01/11/2021
-->
<string_table>
    <!------------- Полковник Кузнецов(Агропром) ----------------->
	<!-- D1 -->
    <string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_first_1">
        <text>Greetings, Comrade Colonel! Milstalker %s has arrived at your command!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_1_0">
	    <text>At ease, soldier.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_1_1">
        <text>Listen carefully, we've received information from an informant in the mercenary ranks. A strange visitor has arrived at the base in Dead City. Strange in that the informant couldn't identify the visitor's faction. On the surface well-equipped and equipped special, but the informant claims that he is not a mercenary. He took some case from Dushman and left, avoiding contact with outsiders. Your job is to find out who this visitor is and what he's doing in the Zone. Is that clear?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_2_1">
	    <text>I have questions about the mission commander.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_4_1">
	    <text>Any recommendations as to where to start looking?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_5_1">
	    <text>Why are we and not SSU doing this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_6_1">
	    <text>Any idea who this visitor is?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_7_1">
	    <text>Did I miss something, can I get a briefing first?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_8_1">
	    <text>There was a report of an attack on a stalker camp in Darkscape a few days ago. Only one survived. He's at the farmhouse on Cordon. There was no mention of attackers. The attackers could have been anyone, bandits, mercs and other scum, or someone connected to our case. Find a way to talk to a surviving stalker and find out more about the attack. It's no big deal, an ordinary event in the Zone, but that's all we've got.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_9_1">
	    <text>I sent a report to headquarters, and enclosed all the information given by the informant. It could take weeks for them to get the SSU operative into the Zone. I got a bad feeling, fighter, that we're running out of time. Something's going on, and it's something trying to hide from our eyes. That's why we'll act on our own, on my own responsibility. You're one of the most experienced military officers, there's no one else I can give this assignment to.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_10_1">
	    <text>And Colonel Degtyarev, he's SSU?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_11_1">
	    <text>The other day Colonel Degtyarev gathered his eagles and headed somewhere to the north of the Zone. I didn't say where exactly, you know the SSU doesn't report to us, they have their own secrets. I heard something about Pripyat outskirts. There is no contact yet, and it is not known when he will appear. We must act now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_12_1">
	    <text>I have my thoughts, but I'll keep them to myself for now. If the information you've found confirms my guesses, we'll talk about it thoroughly.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_13_1">
	    <text>Understood, commander.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_13_2">
	    <text>I got it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_13_3">
	    <text>Understood.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_13_4">
	    <text>Copy that, Colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d1_14_1">
	    <text>No more questions.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D2 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d2_first_1">
	    <text>Report. The stalker is dead, we couldn't get any information.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d2_1_1">
	    <text>Soldier! One more failure and I'll assign this mission to someone more responsible. Remember this! Go to the sawmill and look around for any useful information. Get to it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d2_2_1">
	    <text>Yes, Comrade Colonel! Yes, sir.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D3 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d3_first_1">
	    <text>Commander, I've checked the Sawmill in the Darkscape, it's strange.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d3_1_1">
	    <text>Go on...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d3_2_1">
	    <text>Specialists were working with NATO small arms. By all accounts, mercenaries. I assume that the stalkers were kicked out of the Sawmill, for the attackers needed a base in the Sawmill. They left it, not long before I got there. It's unclear why the mercenaries need a base, in a godforsaken place?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d3_3_1">
	    <text>Hmmm... I wonder... There's nothing strange about it if they're not mercenaries. The Sawmill base is the perfect hiding place to stay hidden. Except a surviving stalker spoiled it for them. All right, let's leave it at that. We'll wait for more information, but for now there are only riddles. I'll let you know when I need you. And yes, stalker. Go see Sergeant Lozhkin. I've ordered you to get new gear.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d3_4_1">
	    <text>Thank you, Comrade Colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D4 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d4_first_1">
	    <text>Comrade Colonel! The task is completed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d4_first_2">
	    <text>Comrade Colonel, any news on our case?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d4_1_1">
	    <text>Take this, soldier, you've earned it. We've had something happen here that requires immediate intervention.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d4_2_1">
	    <text>We've got something that requires immediate intervention.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d4_3_1">
	    <text>I'm listening.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d4_4_1">
	    <text>Before leaving for the north of the Zone, Degtyarev took one squad of fighters from me. Where they were going and what their mission was, I was not told. The men were ordered to keep quiet. Today I got an "SOS" signal from this squad. The message said that they were on the territory of the "Jupiter" plant and had been attacked by unknown people. They're holding out for now, but help is urgently needed. \Your task is to help the fighters. Also find out who these "unknowns" are. They could be our clients we're looking for. Any questions?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d4_5_1">
	    <text>No, commander, I'm on it.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D5 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d5_first_1">
	    <text>The fighters are dead. I was too late to get help. But I did catch the men who eliminated them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d5_1_1">
	    <text>The Jupiter plant isn't far, there's almost no chance of saving them. What did you find out about those who attacked ours?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d5_2_1">
	    <text>Strange stalkers entrenched at the site, blocked the entrances and prepared to hold the defense. It seems they were looking for something in the territory. It's not clear who they were, the equipment is excellent. They acted professionally. Here, a chevron for one of them, the insignia is unfamiliar to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d5_3_1">
	    <text>Hmm... But it's familiar to me. So my hunch is confirmed. Listen carefully, soldier. Now there is an International Study Group in the Zone, in abbreviated form - ISG. Created and exists under the auspices of the UN, but de facto largely controlled by the United States. They work in the Zone quite officially, but if we're talking about eggheads. So, fighter, do your stalkers look like eggheads? That's just it, they don't. They are the fighting wing of the ISG, and they are in the Zone illegally. Illegally, because Ukraine has not allowed international organizations to allow the presence of militarized groups on its territory. The ISG mercenaries, who were sniffing around at the "Jupiter" plant and bumped into ours, most likely it was a chance meeting and they were exposed. Now we know who we're dealing with, it remains to find out: what they forgot in the Zone. As long as the fighter is free, good job. I'll let you know when I need you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d5_4_1">
	    <text>I've got a commander!</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D6 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_first_1">
	    <text>Commander, I've got something!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_1_1">
	    <text>Well, let's make it short, what's on it and where did you get it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_2_1">
	    <text>I was on Kirillov's orders, at our facility, which we guard. The factory above X-18. At the time of my presence, the facility was attacked by ISG, the attack was repulsed, one of the ISG specialists was found with a PDA, on a flash drive part of the information from this PDA.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_3_1">
	    <text>Go on...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_4_1">
	    <text>The flash drive contains maps of the Zone. Where they got them, it's not clear. On the maps are marked various objects, and encrypted comments to the marks. Two objects I have learned, there I ran into squads ISG, this plant "Jupiter" and the entrance to the laboratory "X-18". ISG is looking for something, at various sites in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_5_1">
	    <text>Got it, fighter. The ISG probably bought the maps and all the information they need for their mission from Dushman. Remember that visitor? For secrecy purposes, the data was taken on physical media in the Dead City for fear of intercepting the broadcasts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_6_1">
	    <text>What's our next move, commander? Uh... I wish we could find their hub of operations, where they wouldn't hole up...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_7_1">
	    <text>We need to beef up security at the facilities and keep our ears to the ground. I got hints from Big Earth that we shouldn't interfere with the SSU, they are aware of the ISG's activities. Soldier... Look, there's some big game going on, and we're not welcome at this party of life. So rest up, you did a good job. I'll forward your information to SSU.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d6_8_1">
	    <text>Copy that, Colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D7 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d7_first_1">
	    <text>Reporting as you commanded!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d7_1_1">
	    <text>There's an SSU major standing right there, his identity has been confirmed. Moreover, I contacted Diagtyarev, he was very surprised and alarmed by this major's appearance at the base. The major told the colonel the code: "red 2," I don't know what that means, but after that, I received an unprecedented order from Degtyarev to fully comply with the SSU major's instructions. There's a big operation going on, you'll get the details from the major.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kuznetsov_d7_2_1">
	    <text>I got it. I know this major, he saved my life in the Pripyat Hospital.</text>
	</string>
	<!--------------- Выживший сталкер(Кордон) ------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_first_1">
	    <text>Eh... how come... What am I supposed to do now... </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_1_1">
	    <text>Hello, stalker. We need to talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_2_1">
	    <text>What kind of talk?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_2_2">
	    <text>Military! Oh, yeah... Sidorovich warned me. I have nothing to talk about with the military!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_3_1">
	    <text>I need to know who attacked your unit, at the Sawmill?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_3_2">
	    <text>I either talk to people or shoot them! Choose? I need to know who attacked your unit, at the Sawmill? I'm looking for someone, probably someone who attacked you and they're far from my friends.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_4_1">
	    <text>Oh... Look, I don't know who attacked us. My superior sent me to the Cordon to get provisions. On the way, I had to take a big piss. While I was sitting in the bushes, I heard gunfire at the Sawmill. All died down quickly, tried to contact with their own PDA ... silence. I got scared, man... I ran away from there, bushes and Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_survived_5_1">
	    <text>Yeah, not much. Well, thanks for that. So long, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<!--------------- Сержант Ложкин(Агропром) ------------------->
	<!-- D1 -->
    <string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d1_first_1">
	    <text>Listen, I heard a whisper that you're going to Cordon. I have a favor to ask of you. Take the accounting reports to Major Zhurov at the Southern roadblock, if it's on your way. What do you say, Major won't be indebted?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d1_1_1">
	    <text>All right, give me your reports.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d1_2_1">
	    <text>I don't have time now, find somebody else.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D2 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d2_first_1">
	    <text>Sarge, I'll get my gear.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d2_first_2">
	    <text>Sergeant, is there anything else you want?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d2_1_1">
	    <text>Just a minute. Well... Milstalker %s, on the list, approved by the colonel. Sign here... All right, you're entitled to it:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d2_2_1">
	    <text>Thank you, Sergeant. Well, goodbye.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d2_3_1">
	    <text>Wait a minute, soldier! How'd you like to make some extra money? I had a courier coming in. He said he was at Agroprom and would be here soon. It's been two hours, he's still not here. Find out what happened to him. I'm more interested in the package he was carrying. Should have arrived from the junkyard, so go on the road to the junkyard and look around.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d2_4_1">
	    <text>All right, I'll do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d2_5_1">
	    <text>I don't have time.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D3 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d3_first_1">
	    <text>The courier is dead, killed by mutants. Here's your package.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d3_first_2">
	    <text>Sarge, is there anything else you need?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d3_1_1">
	    <text>Thanks for the package. Your reward. Ah... Too bad I lost my last source of supply.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d3_2_1">
	    <text>Supply source, you say? I wonder if there's anything I can do to help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d3_3_1">
	    <text>Every once in a while, a guard of scientists from Yantar comes by to replenish supplies. They pay well, they're not stingy. Some of them have NATO weapons, and are interested in ammunition for them. As you understand, we almost don't have them in stock, they don't come from the ground, we make do with what we can. Well, my suggestion is that you bring me Nato ammunition, and I'll give you an equal amount of ours, of the same type. I'm not interested in pieces, I'll trade you only packs, minimum quantity 20 packs (280-300 pcs) for the cartridges, and 3 for the underbarrel grenades: \n1. I'll take 300 rounds of 9x19 ammo and give you 320 rounds of 9x18 ammo in return. \n2. I'll take 300 rounds of 5.56x45 ammo and give you an equal amount of 5.45x39. \n3. I'll take 280 rounds of .45 ammo and give you 90 rounds of 9x39. \n4. I'll take 300 rounds of 7.62x51 ammunition and give an equal amount of 7.62x54. \n5. I'll take three M209 grenades, I'll give equal quantity of VOG-25 in return.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d3_4_1">
	    <text>All right, I'll keep that in mind.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D4 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_first_1">
	    <text>I want to trade ammunition.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_1_1">
	    <text>What do you got?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_2_1">
	    <text>I got 9x19mm FMJ ammo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_3_1">
	    <text>I got 9x19mm Dum-dum ammo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_4_1">
	    <text>I got 9x19mm bp ammo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_5_1">
	    <text>There's 5.56x45mm FMJ ammo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_6_1">
	    <text>There are 5.56x45mm EP rounds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_7_1">
	    <text>There are 5.56x45mm EPR rounds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_8_1">
	    <text>There are .45 ACP rounds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_9_1">
	    <text>There are .45 Hydra-shock rounds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_10_1">
	    <text>There are 7.62x51mm NATO FMJ rounds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_11_1">
	    <text>There are 7.62x51mm NATO AP rounds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_12_1">
	    <text>There are M209 underbarrel grenades.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spooner_d4_13_1">
	    <text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<!----------------- Майор Журов(Кордон) ---------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jurov_first_1">
	    <text>Comrade Major! Brought the documents from Agroprom.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jurov_1_1">
	    <text>Ta-ah-ah... Sergeant Lozhkin's accounting report. Thank you, soldier. What do you want for the favor?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jurov_1_2">
	    <text>Ta-rah-rah... Sergeant Lozhkin's accounting report. Thank you, soldier-stalker. Your reward and go, don't rub it in my face.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jurov_2_1">
	    <text>I got a stalker on the farm I need to talk to, and I don't want to get a couple of new bullet holes in me. Can you arrange a truce with the freeloaders?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jurov_3_1">
	    <text>I could use the money.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jurov_4_1">
	    <text>For a favor, I can give you an exclusive truce for two hours. The Stalkers will let you get close and go to their bases, but if you start shooting at them, the truce is over. That's it, you're free to go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jurov_5_1">
	    <text>Thank you, Comrade Major.</text>
	</string>
	<!----------- Ст.лейтенант Кириллов(Агропром) ---------------->
	<!-- D1 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d1_first_1">
	    <text>Soldier, I have a personal favor to ask of you. One of the radios in our Dark Valley unit guarding the facility is malfunctioning. They asked me to send a new one. I need a courier. Can you do that?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d1_1_1">
	    <text>Wrap it up and tie it with a bow, I'll deliver it in the best way.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D2 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d2_first_1">
	    <text>Listen Kirillov, you're a good techie. I have a PDA, and probably with valuable information. Can you unlock it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d2_1_1">
	    <text>We'll see, give it here. Don't count on it being fast, maybe 24 hours, maybe more. I'll let you know when I'm done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d2_2_1">
	    <text>Well, don't wait too long.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D3 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d3_first_1">
	    <text>What's up with the PDA?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d3_1_1">
	    <text>Your PDA wasn't easy, um... it was. It had a special extra security module with a small amount of explosives in it. I tried to figure it out, but I did something wrong, and it's gone. I was only able to remove the external drive, but it was full of information. The cards are all marked up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_kirillov_d3_2_1">
	    <text>Marked cards, huh? Fuck the PDA, don't worry about it. I'm going to see the colonel. Goodbye and thank you.</text>
	</string>
	<!-------- Рандомный командир отряда(Темная долина) ---------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_val_leader_squad_first_1">
	    <text>Greetings military-stalker, why did you come here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_val_leader_squad_1_1">
	    <text>I'll get you a connection, hold the walkie-talkie.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_val_leader_squad_2_1">
	    <text>Thank you for that!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_val_leader_squad_3_1">
	    <text>Don't thank me.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------- Сержант Горобец(Окраины Припяти) ---------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_gorobez_first_1">
	    <text>I was hoping you wouldn't come... I'm sorry...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_gorobez_1_1">
	    <text>What are you talking about?</text>
	</string>
	<!----------- Майор Эрнандес(Окраины Припяти) ---------------->
	<!-- D1 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d1_first_1">
	    <text>You've sabotaged two of our operations, you seem like a fast guy, we need that kind of guy. You work for us, we'll keep you safe. Evacuation from the Zone, a tidy sum in an account in any country in the world. You don't have much choice, there are only two options.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d1_1_1">
	    <text>What is the second one?</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D2 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d2_first_1">
	    <text>Any other questions?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d2_1_1">
	    <text>I think I'll refrain.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d2_2_1">
	    <text>I don't have much time, so I don't have time to bother with you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d2_3_1">
	    <text>(silence...)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d2_4_1">
	    <text>All right, I'm not having a heart-to-heart with you. I'll give you 30 minutes to think about it. We'll talk again later. Maybe with a little more passion, it's up to you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_leader_d2_5_1">
	    <text>(silence...)</text>
	</string>
	<!----------- Лейтенант Годунов(Окраины Припяти) ------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_agent_d1_first_1">
	    <text>Listen up! I'm an SSU major. Another day, I wouldn't have lifted a finger to save your skin and risk my cover with the ISG. But it looks like today's your day. Our whole operation is screwed up. ISG somehow got wind of a stalker they weren't supposed to know about. And also about the meeting of Degtyarev with this stalker. Sent a special group to eliminate Degtyarev and capture a stalker. The meeting will take place in the hostel. The special group plans to go in from the back entrance, and squeeze out Degtyarev and his archrivals with combat, to an open position for the sniper in the courtyard. The sniper will be waiting in the house opposite.\n You owe me your life! Your pay is to warn the colonel about the trap. Remember the phrase: "Death does not wait, nor should life wait." Without the code, Degtyarev might put a bullet in your forehead, just in case. And also, I have information of particular importance, betray through communication will not work, ISG pelenguet all frequencies. I hid the case in a department store, and waited for the right opportunity, and you are my opportunity. You'll give Degtyarev the information about the case in the department store. Do you understand?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_isg_agent_d1_1_1">
	    <text>Yes, I'll do everything. И ... Thank you.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------- Полковник Дегтярёв(Окраины Припяти) ------------->
	<!-- D1 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d1_first_1">
	    <text>You need to tell me something that explains why you're here. You went where you shouldn't have gone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d1_1_1">
	    <text>Hold on, Colonel, I have a love letter for you from your friend, "Death does not wait, nor should life wait."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d1_2_1">
	    <text>Okay, now I trust you a little more, and it looks like you saved our hides. And thank you very much for that. Under what circumstances did you learn the code, and what information do you have for me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d1_3_1">
	    <text>At the Hospital, I was captured by the ISG. An ISG officer, unexpectedly shot my guards, gave me back my belongings and weapons. Called himself an SSU major. Gave me an assignment to warn you, Colonel, about a trap the ISG was preparing and gave me a code phrase. I rushed as fast as I could, but didn't make it in time, and made an independent decision to eliminate the main threat, a sniper in your rear. One more thing, an "ISG officer" told me to tell you about a case he had hidden in the department store, according to him it contained information of a special importance on the activities of the ISG.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d1_4_1">
	    <text>I see, it looks like the agent was right to risk his cover. Since I don't have people here, you'll have to take the case. I'll meet you at the Agroprom base. Do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d1_5_1">
	    <text>Yes, Comrade Colonel!</text>
	</string>
	<!-------------- Полковник Дегтярёв(Агропром) ---------------->
	<!-- D2 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d2_first_1">
	    <text>Did you get the case?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d2_1_1">
	    <text>Yes, here it is.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d2_2_1">
	    <text>Good, this is for your help. You're a good soldier, I've decided to put you in my special group. You'll report directly to me. Kuznetsov will arrange the transfer papers. In the meantime, I'll contact you later.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d2_3_1">
	    <text>Yes, Comrade Colonel!</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D3 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d3_first_1">
	    <text>I wanted to ask...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d3_2_1">
	    <text>Through the agent we must know where the ISG's operations center is, why don't we just finish them off?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d3_3_1">
	    <text>I was able to find out that the ISG are inspecting various objects in the Zone, and are looking for something on purpose. What do we know about the main purpose of the ISG in the Zone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d3_4_1">
	    <text>That stalker in Pripyat, I recognized him; it is a Rifleman! Why is he so important to the ISG?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d3_5_1">
	    <text>Destroying the base will only delay the problem, not solve it. The ISG will throw in a new group, which may be more successful. Despite the fact that the ISG paramilitary group is illegally in the Zone, destroying them would cause an international scandal. Our job is to get any information for the diplomats that will generally discredit the ISG's activities in the Zone. After that, they will leave on their own, or we will help them, and no one will say a word at the UN.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d3_6_1">
	    <text>The SSU analysts have known their purpose since the arrival of the ISG. The ISG is looking for any information that would give even a hint that The Zone is the result of the development of weapons of mass destruction and is a threat to international security. It doesn't have to be the truth. It is important for the ISG to initiate an international investigation into The Zone and, under the weight of the material obtained, to force Ukraine to give full access to The Zone to international organizations to conduct an investigation. This would effectively deprive Ukraine of its monopoly right to The Zone, and control would pass to UN. ISG, in turn, would receive carte blanche to conduct any of its operations. And we are likely to be strongly advised to get out of The Zone until the investigation is completed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d3_7_1">
	    <text>If it ends up in the hands of the ISG, it will be a total disaster and a failure of the entire operation. But that's not your concern. My advice to you: forget about this stalker and everything connected with him. You'll live longer.</text>
	</string>
    <!-- D4 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_first_1">
	    <text>Stalker %s has arrived on your orders.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_1_1">
	    <text>At ease! Let's cut the formalities. There's a mission for you. Our agent has given us a wealth of information on ISG activities. Now I am interested in one of the groups, the agent could not find out the purpose of their mission, it is kept secret from the other members of the ISG. According to his observations, this group periodically every 2 days, leave the base and return after 24 hours. Your task is to find out what their purpose is.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_2_1">
	    <text>There's too little information, commander!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_3_1">
	    <text>That's not all. Earlier, a mercenary informant told us about an ISG group that appears periodically in the Dead City. The Dushman strictly warned us to approach the lone house in the southwest of Dead City, and to make contact with them. I hadn't paid much attention to this information before, assuming that the ISG was supplying there. But there seems to be a connection. As long as there's a window of time, go check the place out quietly, and leave a bookmark there, a tape recorder. Exactly two days from now, pick it up and bring it to me. Maybe something will come of it. Any questions?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_3_2">
	    <text>Any other questions?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_4_1">
	    <text>Any questions about the assignment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_5_1">
	    <text>No questions, I'll do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_7_1">
	    <text>Why a tape recorder, Colonel? Are we homeless? Don't we have more advanced radio transmitters?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d4_8_1">
	    <text>We're working against an organization that's far better equipped than SSU. They'll detect any radio plantations with a detector. We just scare them off, they'll change locations. Kirillov built a recorder specifically for this mission that picks up the sound and starts recording. It does not emit any radio waves, so it is virtually impossible to detect.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D5 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d5_first_1">
	    <text>Mission accomplished.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d5_1_1">
	    <text>Well done. Separately from you, I left observers who were videotaping what was going on. Now I need time to analyze all the audio and video material with a technician. The ISG is small, but they are supported by mercenaries who are well paid. We're getting some disturbing information, the ISG and the mercenaries are concentrating in Limansk. You can probably see why. They're targeting the CNPP. And it could jeopardize our entire operation. Thanks to you turning off the Brain Burner, I've sent a squad of our fighters to the CNPP. Their orders are to wait for you, and then accompany and follow your orders. Your task is to prevent the ISG from reaching the Sarcophagus. The main objective is to eliminate the ISG group, the rest is of little interest to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d5_2_1">
	    <text>Yes, Comrade Colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D6 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d6_first_1">
	    <text>The ISG has been eliminated.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d6_1_1">
	    <text>Good work. We've finished analyzing the materials. The ISG has established a black channel of distribution and supply through mercenaries. In the house where you set up the recorder, they were trading weapons and ammunition for artifacts. Well... UN doesn't like that their "hand-to-hand" organization is a smuggling ring. Looks like we have enough information and it's time for our diplomatic corps to get to work. I'm going to Big Earth, and you're temporarily at Kuznetsov's disposal until I return.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_degtyarev_d6_2_1">
	    <text>Give them hell there, commander.</text>
	</string>
	<!--------------- Майор Верещагин(Агропром) ------------------>
	<!-- D1 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_vereshagin_d1_first_1">
	    <text>I'll outline the situation. You guys were shitting your pants a little bit, so I had to step in. While you were messing around with the CNPP group, which was also a cover, the main squad, along with their eggheads, got into the X-8 and apparently found something they didn't need to find. So, Hernandez, the head of the ISG combat mission in the Zone, ordered a wrap up and prepare to evacuate. You smell that, fighter?! I smell something fierce. The head of SSU, on operational communication, gave the go-ahead to liquidate the ISG headquarters, and not to let the information they had dug up, all this time, get out of The Zone. The Ukraine will face diplomatic consequences after that, but that is much less important than the information that the ISG might have, and if it gets out to the UN.\n the ISG chose for their base, a great place to lay low, but disgusting in terms of strategy. We locked them on the side of Pripyat and on the side of Jupiter, it was not difficult. The mouse, it's not going to slip through. Now for the hard part, what you have to do. Lead an assault team of experienced fighters and clean up this rat's nest. You go in, anyone who shoots at you has to be eliminated. Or should I put someone else in charge, and you want your mama?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_vereshagin_d1_1_1">
	    <text>Try to stop me, Comrade Major!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_vereshagin_d1_2_1">
	    <text>Good attitude, fighter, I approve. Get to it, time is running out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_vereshagin_d1_3_1">
	    <text>Yes, sir.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- D2 -->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_vereshagin_d2_first_1">
	    <text>Comrade Major...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_vereshagin_d2_1_1">
	    <text>I've already been informed by radio that the ISG operations center has been destroyed. I've sent a trophy team and SSU operatives, they'll take everything of value there. Some scattered units of ISG probably still remain in the Zone, but without a unified center of coordination and supply, they are not a threat, and over time, melt into other groups, or try to evacuate on their own. You did a good job. We all did a good job. Our operation is over. The details of the operation are state secrets, so keep your mouth shut if you don't want to lose it. If you talk, SSU will be interested in you. This is from me, a personal gift:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_vereshagin_d2_2_1">
	    <text>Thank you, Comrade Major.</text>
	</string>
	<!------------ Рандомный командир отряда(CNPP) --------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_aes_leader_squad_first_1">
	    <text>Reporting! We did reconnaissance, observers report the monochrome are holding the main entrance, the mercs are closing in on them. The fight is going on with varying success, but the Monolith is pulling its forces together and soon the merks will be deflated.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_aes_leader_squad_1_1">
	    <text>Mmm... where's the ISG group?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_aes_leader_squad_2_1">
	    <text>I can't say. The scouts haven't located them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_aes_leader_squad_3_1">
	    <text>Something's not right...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_aes_leader_squad_4_1">
	    <text>One of our scouts stopped communicating. His job is to control the road to the hospital. His last contact was an hour ago and he hasn't responded.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_aes_leader_squad_5_1">
	    <text>We don't have much time, there's no time to check, so we'll have to take our chances and go blind. There's nothing for us to do here anyway, so we'd better let the measures keep entertaining the monochrome ones. Get the boys up, let's move out!</text>
	</string>
	<!-------------- Рандомный агент SSU(Юпитер) ----------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jup_agent_d1_first_1">
	    <text>Assault team on alert. Shall we start the assault?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jup_agent_d1_1_1">
	    <text>Let's go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_jup_agent_d1_2_1">
	    <text>Not yet.</text>
	</string>
	<!--------------- Сущность(Темная лощина) -------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spirit_d1_first_1">
	    <text>What do we got? Traces of blood outside the building. Lack of shell casings means the sentry was taken by surprise and didn't return fire. Let's see what happens next...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spirit_d1_1_1">
	    <text>To continue...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_spirit_d2_first_1">
	    <text>Stalkers inside the building, did not immediately realize what was happening, and were attacked from two entrances, with almost no resistance. 5.56x45 NATO shell casings... looks like mercenaries. Hmm... the attack was two days ago, and the coals in the fire are still warm. The attackers were camped here and I missed them for a while. Whoever it was, they're not here anymore, so it's time to get back to Kuznetsov.</text>
	</string>
	<!------------------- Общие диалоги -------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_1_1">
	    <text>Got it, commander.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_1_2">
	    <text>I got it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_1_3">
	    <text>Understood.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_1_4">
	    <text>Roger, Colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_2_1">
	    <text>Go ahead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_2_2">
	    <text>Go ahead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_2_3">
	    <text>Go ahead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_dialog_all_3_1">
	    <text>I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<!----------------------- Notes ------------------------------>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_spooner">
		<text>A note from Sergeant Lozhkin.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_spooner_text">
		<text> \Lozhkin proposes an exchange: I take 300 rounds of 9x19 ammo, I give you 320 rounds of 9x18; I take 300 rounds of 5.56x45 ammo, I give you an equal amount of 5.45x39; I take 280 rounds of .45. .45 ammo, I will give 90 rounds of 9x39 ammo in return; \n - I will take 300 rounds of 7.62x51 ammo, I will give an equal amount of 7.62x54 ammo in return; \n - I will take 5 M209 grenades, I will give an equal amount of VOG-25 grenades in return. </text>
	</string>
</string_table>
