<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<!--
    Storyline: Hidden Threat
	Version:   1.0
    Autor:     Longreed
	Last Edit: 01/11/2021
-->
<string_table>
    
	<!---------------------- Task 1 ------------------------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_0_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: The Beginning</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>The commander gave a mission: to find the black cat in the dark room.\n Ask Colonel Kuznetsov about the mission in more detail.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_1_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Surviving Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>There was no further substantial information from Kuznetsov concerning my assignment. Also, the colonel instructed me to check what happened to the stalkers in the Darkscape. At the farm, which is on Cordon, there is a stalker who survived the attack on the Sawmill. Will have to use disguise to talk to him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_2_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Return to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_2_descr">
	    <text>Something went wrong and the stalker is dead. Inform Kuznetsov of the failure.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_3_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Get to the Sawmill in the Darkscape</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_3_descr">
	    <text>It's worth looking around the Sawmill yourself, looking for any useful information that might shed some light on the events that took place here in the recent past.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_4_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Examine the Sawmill Building</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_4_descr">
	    <text>It's worth looking around the Sawmill yourself, searching for any useful information that might shed some light on what happened here in the recent past.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_5_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Return to Colonel Kuznetsov</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_1_stage_5_descr">
	    <text>Found not much, to say the least. Nothing more to do here, it's time to go back to the commander with a report.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Task 2 ------------------------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_2_stage_0_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Disable Brain Scorcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_2_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>"Brain Scorcher" is seriously hampering military operations in the north. Kuznetsov has given a difficult assignment: to deal with it. The scientists on Yantar must have already figured out a way to do it. We need to talk to Sakharov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_2_stage_1_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Return to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_2_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>"Brain Scorcher is disabled. Remains to report to the colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Task 3 ------------------------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_0_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Get to the Jupiter plant.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>An "SOS" signal was received, from the squad that Degtyarev had sent, on a secret mission. It was reported that the squad was attacked on the territory of the factory "Jupiter" by unknown and they urgently need fire support.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_1_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Inspect the production facilities of the "Jupiter" plant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>At the entrance of the plant is empty, from the administrative premises, the same sound. We need to go further into the production facilities.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_2_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Examine the bodies of the attackers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_2_descr">
	    <text>Soldiers are dead, could not be saved. What mission they performed at the plant, only Degtyarev knows. Unknown stalkers gave me a warm welcome. They were looking for something at the plant. Hmm... Chevrons with symbols unknown to me. Perhaps the colonel knows more. We should get at least one.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_3_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_3_stage_3_descr">
	    <text>The unknown stalkers, had patches with unknown to me symbols. Perhaps the colonel knows more about them.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Task 4 ------------------------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_0_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Lieutenant Kirillov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>Lieutenant Kirillov asked me to stop by and see him. Find out what he needs from me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_1_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Take the radio military in the Dark Valley</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>All it takes is a little work as the letter carrier Pechkin. I think I can handle it. A detachment of military guards the entrance to the "X-18" in the Dark Valley, and waiting for my package.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_2_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Repel the ISG attack.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_2_descr">
	    <text>Oh, man! Wrong time, wrong place. I need to organize a defense.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_3_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Examine the attackers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_3_descr">
	    <text>Alright. Alive and well, that's good. We need to examine the attackers for useful information.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_4_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Lieutenant Kirillov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_4_descr">
	    <text>Found a PDA on one of the ISG mercenaries, most likely it was the commander of the group. PDA is blocked, our technician should be able to cope with this, let him cast spells, maybe come out hacking.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_5_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Waiting for Kirillov to unlock the PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_5_descr">
	    <text>Kirillov said that the hacking will not take much time. A day or more. We can mind our own business in the meantime.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_6_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Lieutenant Kirillov</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_6_descr">
	    <text>The technician reports that the PDA seems to have been hacked.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_7_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Colonel Kuznetsov</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_4_stage_7_descr">
	    <text>On the maps from the PDA, there were marks that I am already familiar with. Jupiter Plant, Plant over X-18. That's where I met up with the ISG. Consequently, the other markers are also the targets of the ISG, I need to report this to Kuznetsov.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Task 5 ------------------------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_0_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Meet Sergeant Gorobetz.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>The sergeant spotted the ISG group and asked for help. The meeting place is the Hospital in the outskirts of Pripyat. I have nothing else to do, no more tasks the colonel did not give.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_1_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: The Mouse in the Mousetrap.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_2_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Destroy ISG Sniper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_2_descr">
	    <text>The ISG plans to eliminate Colonel Degtyarev. He doesn't stand a chance. The ISG task force has already been dispatched a long time ago, and I probably won't have time to warn the colonel. But I can take a risk and destroy the sniper and prevent the trap from slamming.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_3_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Provide fire support to the SSU detachment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_3_descr">
	    <text>The sniper is eliminated. SSU detachment, led by Degtyarev, attacked by the ISG assault group, you need to rush to their aid.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_4_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Colonel Degtyarev</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_4_descr">
	    <text>The ISG group has been eliminated. Talk to the colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_5_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Find the case in the department store</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_5_descr">
	    <text>The colonel instructed him to retrieve the briefcase from the department store, left by an SSU agent.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_6_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Take the case to the Agroprom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_5_stage_6_descr">
	    <text>Degtyarev is waiting for me with the case at the military base Agroprom.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Task 6 ------------------------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_0_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Colonel Degtyarev</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>Received an order from the colonel, return to the base and go to him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_1_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Bookmark the Dead City</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>The task is not dusty, get to the Dead City, and in a house that stands alone in the south-west to lay the recorder.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_2_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Wait 2 days.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_2_descr">
	    <text>The bookmark is done. Two days to pick it up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_3_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: To pick up the bookmark from Dead City.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_3_descr">
	    <text>2 days have passed, you need to pick up the recorder and take it to Colonel Degtyarev.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_4_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Return to Degtyarev.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_4_descr">
	    <text>I have the recorder, you need to take it to Colonel Degtyarev.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_5_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to the squad leader at CNPP.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_5_descr">
	    <text>The ISG are planning to break through the monochrome ones at CNPP. They're most likely already there, and my job is to keep them out of Sarcophagus. My support squad is waiting for me at the arranged location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_6_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Go to the northwest of CNPP.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_6_descr">
	    <text>At the main entrance, only mercenaries were found. The ISG could not be found. Squad leader reported that one of his scouts stopped contact. He may have been detected and destroyed, Since the main entrance is not our main target, it is worth checking the road from the Hospital.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_7_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Eliminate the ISG team.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_7_descr">
	    <text>It's just as I suspected. The mercenaries were distracting the main monochrome forces, and the group of ISG, quietly came in from the side of the Hospital, not attracting attention. To Combat!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_8_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Report success to Degtyarev</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_6_stage_8_descr">
	    <text>The mission was completed, the group of ISGs was destroyed, and now I have to report to the colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Task 7 ------------------------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_0_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Report to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>In the absence of Degtyarev, I now once again obey Kuznetsov, and why did he need me? Not a day's peace ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_1_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Talk to Major Vereshchagin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>To say I was surprised is nothing to say. Major Vereshchagin is the same SSU agent who saved my life in Pripyat, I recognized him. What could have happened to bring him here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_2_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: To get to the entrance to the Pripyat Underground</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_2_descr">
	    <text>It's about time I was done with the ISG My assault squad is waiting for me at the entrance to the Pripyat Underground, on the Jupiter side.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_3_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Entering the Pripyat Underground.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_3_descr">
	    <text>It's about time we were done with ISG...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_4_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Eliminate any enemy presence in the Pripyat Underground</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_4_descr">
	    <text>It's about time we put an end to ISG...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_5_title">
	    <text>Hidden Threat: Report success to Major Vereshchagin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_task_7_stage_5_descr">
	    <text>ISG is done, the assault was a success, it's time to report to Major Vereshchagin.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Second Task 1 ------------------------------------>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_second_task_1_stage_0_title">
	    <text>[HT]Southern Checkpoint: Hand over the documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_second_task_1_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>Give the accounting reports to Major Zhurov, at the Southern roadblock Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------------------- Second Task 2 ------------------------------------>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_second_task_2_stage_0_title">
	    <text>[HT]Agroprom: Find courier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_second_task_2_stage_0_descr">
	    <text>Sergeant Lozhkin instructed to find the courier, which is somewhere lost on the road, to the base from the dump. Sergeant is more interested in the package that the courier was carrying for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_second_task_2_stage_1_title">
	    <text>[HT]Agroprom: Return the package to Lozhkin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_second_task_2_stage_1_descr">
	    <text>Sergeant Lozhkin is instructed to find the courier, who got lost somewhere on the road, to the base from the Dump. The sergeant is more interested in the package the courier was carrying for him.</text>
	</string>
	<!---------- Tips message для "Hidden Threat" ---------------------------->
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_start">
	    <text>%s, your presence is required at the base. There is an urgent assignment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_task_2_start">
	    <text>Milstalker, our case is still a dead end. But there's a difficult assignment for you. Our northern operations are severely hampered by the Brain Scorcher. Talk to Sakharov on Yantar and find a way to disable it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_task_3_start">
	    <text>Milstalker, come see me, I need to talk to you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_task_4_start">
	    <text>%s, come in for a minute, we need to talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_task_4_stg_6_msg">
	    <text>%s, about your PDA. Come on over, we got something to talk about.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_task_5_start">
	    <text>Hey %s, long time no see. I spotted a group of ISG I can't do this alone, I need help. If you have the guts to go to the hospital in the outskirts of Pripyat, maybe even earn new stripes from the bosses.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_task_6_start">
	    <text>Milstalker %s, orders are to arrive at the base and come straight to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_task_7_start">
	    <text>Milstalker %s, orders to report to me immediately!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_armistice_title">
	    <text>Received:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_armistice_msg">
	    <text>%s: free stalkers - 2 hours</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_armistice_path">
	    <text>Armistice</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_armistice_start">
	    <text>%s asked for you. We opened a free pass to our bases for 2 hours. Let's not do anything stupid, if you want to live. Our boys, they don't like warriors very much.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_msg_armistice_end">
	    <text>%s truce is over.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_spooner_notes_title">
	    <text>Received:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_spooner_notes_descr">
	    <text>New PDA entry: A note from Sgt. Lozhkin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_darkvalley_msg_header">
	    <text>Military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_darkvalley_msg_text">
	    <text>I see the enemy! To battle!</text>
	</string>
    <!------------------------------------------------------------------------->
    <string id="st_sl_hidden_threat_map_spot_cf">
	    <text>Place of interest</text>
	</string>

</string_table>